Contact

7096622087 (Mobile) mayankpadaliya91@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mayankpadaliya-9a33a8132 (LinkedIn) www.instagram.com/mayankhp/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Interior Architecture Architectural Design AutoCAD

Languages

Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Elementary)
Gujarati (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Tokyo Institute of Technology -Japanese Architecture and Structural Design

Introduction to BIM and Revit Workshop

WREC STUDENTS
ARCHITECTURE COMPETITION

Harvard University Graduate School Of Design - The Architectural Imagination

Fellow Life Member

Mayank Padaliya

Architect | Entrepreneur | Learning Gen ai and automation Vadodara, Gujarat, India

Summary

I've been interested in the construction field for many years. I like my job so much that I decided to start my own building business which is still running well. As a second company I have gained more experience in other fields, and I am trying to improve them as much as I can.

Experience

Techfocal Enterprises LLP
Director
December 2023 - Present (1 year 6 months)
Vadodara, Gujarat, India

Jayatilal M Padaliya Managing Director September 2023 - Present (1 year 9 months) Vadodara, Gujarat, India

Shreeji Krupa Builder Co-Owner August 2023 - Present (1 year 10 months) Rajpipala

Faculty of Architecture & Planning - Parul University Architectural Intern November 2022 - February 2023 (4 months) Vadodara Taluka, Gujarat, India

Sangath: Vastushilpa Consultants, Ahmedabad Volunteer June 2022 - August 2022 (3 months)

Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India

Aasqaure Architects

Legal Assistant Intern December 2018 - April 2019 (5 months)

Vadodara Area, India

Education

Parul University

Bachelor of Architecture - BArch, Architecture · (July 2019 - June 2024)

Instituto Superior Técnico

Mestrado Integrado em Arquitetura, Architecture · (February 2023 - July 2023)

Wroclaw University of Science and Technology

Erasmus, Architecture · (February 2020 - June 2020)

Gujarat Technological University, Ahmedbabd

Diploma, Architecture Assistantship · (July 2016 - May 2019)

Bright day school Vadodara

Secondary School, 10th Standard (May 2016)